class Hele {
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> thirdMonthly = <Map<String, dynamic>>[
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'goals',
      'question': 'results or dreams that want to be achieved.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'home management',
      'question': 'the process of properly maintaining a home.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'needs',
      'question':
          'things necessary to live a healthy life such as food and shelter.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'values',
      'question':
          "guiding principles that determine one's idea of good behavior and conduct.",
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'wants',
      'question':
          "things that are not basic needs but enhance one's quality of life.",
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'home management',
      'question': 'is the method of properly maintaining a home.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'planning',
      'question':
          'this is the first step of the process before any activity takes place.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'organizing',
      'question':
          'this second stage involves arranging plans for a specific activity so that it goes well with other activities that are going on or yet to be done.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'controlling',
      'question':
          'this is the third stage where the plan is implemented and monitored.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'evaluating',
      'question':
          'this is the last yet ongoing process of checking and assessing expected outcomes to determine what was accomplished.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'family goals',
      'question':
          'these meaningful and realistic goals can change and follow a certain order of priority.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'family values',
      'question': 'this refers to the guiding principles of a family.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'family needs',
      'question':
          'every family needs important things such as clothing, food, shelter, education, water, and health services, which are considered basic needs.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'clothing',
      'question':
          'is necessary for every person to be a dignified human being.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'food',
      'question': 'is the fuel you need to survive.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'shelter',
      'question':
          'is one of the most important needs of a family to live with ease.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'education',
      'question':
          'is essential for every family in order to raise successful, intelligent, and creative children.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'health', 'question': 'is wealth.'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'security or protection',
      'question':
          'is needed, especially during these times when danger is more common, whether physically or virtually.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'effective communication',
      'question': 'is the foundation of great relationships.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'love', 'question': 'binds families together.'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'order',
      'question':
          'is also needed in every family to keep things running smoothly.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'access to information technology',
      'question': "has become a basic need in today's modern world.",
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'family resources',
      'question':
          'these refer to the things that the family can use to meet their needs.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'human resources',
      'question': 'are the ones that exist within an individual.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'abilities and skills',
      'question':
          'resources that may be inherited, acquired, or developed through practice to achieve particular goals.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'attitude',
      'question': 'opinions or feelings of people that may hinder.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'energy',
      'question': 'refers to both the mental and physical power of a person.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'knowledge',
      'question':
          'refers to awareness of things to be able to achieve dreams or goals.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'time',
      'question':
          'the 24 hours a day that all people have but are used differently based on goals and personal choice.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'non-human resources',
      'question':
          'are tangible things or objects that exist outside of the individual.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'family income',
      'question': 'it includes money, material goods, and services earned.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'wages and salary',
      'question':
          'this is the most common form of household income earned through work.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'investment income',
      'question': 'means spending some money to make more money.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'government assistance',
      'question':
          'when you and your family experience financial struggles, you may apply for this to have additional income sources.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'retirement income',
      'question':
          'is the amount of money that elderly people receive when they retire at a certain age after working for a minimum number of months.',
    }
  ];
}
